Hello friends, once again you are
very welcome to our channel
and if you take it directly then there is a very
good good news for you, a
wonderful Diwali offer has come, in that
all the VLEs will get a printer for free, it is a
3D printer, you will get it absolutely free,
so what do you have to do for that, in
exchange for what work you will be given the printer
and what process do you have to do, I will show you the entire process
live, friends, but
okay, as always, I would like to make a small
request that if you are new on our channel, then
you must subscribe to our channel
and
also press the bell icon, friends, and if you have
any problem, you
can comment in the comment box below the video,
friends, if you are serious then if you have
any problem with your Deputy SP, then you
can come and see it on our portal,
friends, and if there is any problem with DJ or any other friend or relative, then
also you can
comment in the comment box below the video, friends,
those who commented have definitely received a reply
and have been shown in the live video on Facebook
and yours too are one of them  If you have any problem
then you
can like and watch any type of video on our channel
friends and if you don't find the video then
comment in the comment box and
also comment from which state you are watching,
whatever your problem is, it is applicable in that state,
friend, it is not applicable for that also, I will solve it in MB and
tell you friends, so come on friends today
we are watching what is the Diwali Dhamaka
Dhamaka offer, so let me
show you from the official side,
see this, the news has come from the official side,
come tomorrow friend, there is a
Diwali offer on Cyber ​​Security, this is an
amazing Diwali offer, under the path of Cyber ​​Security and
C Lead and 3D Printer course,
every candidate
gets a 3D printer on registration, hurry up
this offer is valid only till 30th November,
friend before 30th November if you register 50
candidates for 3D printer
then you will definitely get this 3D printer, this
3D printer will reach you for Rs. 2000, this
Bishop of yours will reach there and the main  It will become
aromatic free, so this
is very good for you friends, you have to
work for it, this printer is for winning,
you are getting that much benefit for free,
so you have to
understand that you have to register 50 candidates
and what to do for that, so
you open your browser
and open your ad digital seva portal,
I will tell you
how to go there and from where you have to book, so
you have to open the digital seva portal here
and after opening the digital seva portal
you will be asked for CID password,
friends if you have taken sugar then watch this video
otherwise you can skip it, hello
friends this is just an offer and you
can avail the above benefit only if you are a VLE and if
you are not a VLE then you have a 3D printer, you can
go to the VLE center to get the draw done, you are getting a little commission for it, there
is a printer for that but
you can get it free from there, you have some benefit in
that friends, there is still a discount like Diwali,
3D printer will be made available to you with such a discount on 3D
printer, so  Friends,
you have to enter this BCC CID and password
and if you do not have the CID password
then you cannot open it, so friends, it is
very important to have your Common Service Center ID to open the Digital Seva Portal, as soon
as you come
here, friends, you have to come to the service,
after coming to the service, you have to
write 3D printer in the search box, you will just delete three more,
then only you will see the
service here, see, let me do a
little Amazon, it is
showing you the 3D printer CSP service here, from that that
service will be in front of you, write 3D so much and
you have to click on the check here and
as soon as you click on the check here,
you will be taken to how to register for it, so
many services will be available here, but
first you will see the appointment for 3D printer, the
link is on it, you have to
click on it, see
whichever 3D printer is shown here, friends,
you have to
book for the one you want to buy and you  Or if you want to
see the details from here then you can see it, then if you want to buy
any printer from this then
you can see it here,
all of them are written here, so you can see its
details by using [Music] here whichever one you want to buy, like you want to buy this, and as soon as you
see the details, you can see what are the
facilities of the printer in it,
how much is it, it is shown completely,
any front or back is near in it and you can
see it here,
after reading it completely, what is its net waste,
it is of 30 kg, that is also told to you
and what all is there in it,
you can open it from the print and see it, but
to book
you will have to click on New below and as soon as you
click on New, you have to
write your name here, whatever your name is,
friends, write it here and
as soon as you write the name, after that you have to
fill whatever process you want next, the
name will appear here or your father's name will appear
Also in the father's uniform, here
you will get the mobile number and this is your
email ID and this is your state which has to be done
and from here you have to use the district,
Prince, the district from which you are from, you have to make
it 24 and here you have to
click on your complete address and here
you have to enter the pin code number and address friends, it is
very important for you to have your mobile number in this dress also, so after the pin code number below, you should enter the
mobile number young man or you should enter
your mobile number in this dress also
friends and here your pin code
is post code, enter it here and here from here
you have to enter the shipping address
again, this is also
important, from Faizabad where you are doing shop
or you have to give this technique to anyone,
that too, from here it
recognizes you, that is, if you are writing it, it will
come here and if you
want to give it to someone else, then for this, half subscribe,
we have written the name above,
subscribe
flag friends and where do you want to
shop from below, for that your
address or aromatic will be given and you have to enter here from where, from
which district  Show the state from which you are
viewing,
only on doing state 24, the main head
of the state level, that district of the use office will be
shown here and the one from
where you are going to shift, from where you will get the booking
done, will come here
and after coming here you have to
click on the next button queue friends and get it
completely completed, friends do
not hurry in this, if there is any problem then
talk to us and see this in front of you, the
payment will be deducted from the Chinese wallet,
for that you have to click on pay queue here,
like your payment is very important to be in your CID wallet,
if you have
payment in that particular wallet then only you
can complete it, if the
payment is not complete in your CSC wallet then it will
tell you like this, delay in hidden wallet
balance, so it is very important for you to enter your wallet balance first, so
friends, those whom you want to book,
put the amount in the wallet and
after that you can deduct the payment from the wallet,
for deducting the payment in gold, you will be
asked for oil at CSC ID here and C
I  After entering the de-password, you have to
enter the gold pin and after that your payment will be
submitted and your payment will be completely done,
so friends,
today there is something seriously special for you which is absolutely amazing and
I was telling you about it by liking the video
and despite that if you have any
problem then you can come to our channel and watch it
friends and if you like this video even a little bit then
you
must like and share it
because friends if you like and share it,
we get a lot of encouragement for which
we keep bringing updates and
those who have not yet subscribed to our Jeera Ka Mixture
Centre channel then
definitely press the bell icon along with subscribe
so that you always keep getting the notification of our videos
friends, now friends, let's
meet again in the next video, till then I
seek your permission, this is all
for today, Jai Hind Jai Bharat